<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ekaputra</title>
    <link>https://ekaputra.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ekaputra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 19:35:21 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ekaputra.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://ekaputra.dev/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 19:35:21 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ekaputra.dev/projects/</guid>
      <description>These are some projects that I&amp;rsquo;ve been working-on on my spare time, all of them are open source because we&amp;rsquo;re all love open source software don&amp;rsquo;t we?. For a complete list please check my GitHub account.
Gatra Bali, a news reader app built using Flutter Gatra Bali is a news reader app (for Balinese news only) built using Flutter, initially this app was just a test project to see how is it feel developing mobile app using Flutter and my conclusion is I like it so much :) so I turned it into a production app that can be downloaded here (currently only available on Android).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ekaputra.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ekaputra.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Experienced software engineer with a passion for developing scalable software system. With 9+ years of experiences from developing simple websites for clients to working on backend/API services for apps that serve millions of users.
Always eager to learn something new (techniques or programming languages), implements best practices in software development. Have a strong can-do attitude, effective communication and problem solving skills. Happy to work in a team or independently.
I was born in a small village in Bali, Indonesia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>